myorangeclerk.com 2018-10-04

# My Orange Clerk Home

### Our Privacy Statement

**Orange County Clerk of Courts Website Privacy Policy**  
The Orange County Clerk of Courts respects the privacy of our website users and is dedicated to making your experience on our website and with our organization the best it can be. The following Privacy Statement describes how information is collected and used from visitors to the Orange County Clerk of Court website. This Privacy Statement does not apply to links provided to other sites.

**Disclaimer**  
By using the services provided by the Orange County Clerk of Courts website, the user agrees to indemnify and hold harmless Orange County Clerk of Courts and anyone involved in storing, retrieving or displaying this information for any damage of any type that may be caused by retrieving this information over the internet.

This website does not provide legal advice of any kind. If you require legal advice, please consult a qualified attorney of your choosing. The information offered on this website is for the convenience of our customers.

**Information Collected and How It Is Used**  
The Orange County Clerk of Courts’ website uses web analytics to create summary statistics about the use of the website. The resulting statistics are used to assess the types of information that is of most interest to users, to refine design specifications and to identify system performance issues. When accessing the Orange County Clerk of Courts site, the webserver recognizes only the internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. The data collected do not reveal any personal information such as your personal e-mail address. The information that is gathered relates to site traffic, access times and dates and pages visited while at the site. The collection of information such as date and time is done for the purpose of website optimization. This information is not shared with other organizations.

The Orange County Clerk of Courts provides certain online transactions on our website. For example, it is possible to look up case information, bid on foreclosed properties or pay traffic fines using our secure online process. In each case, the information requested is the identical information that would be requested if you performed the same transaction in person rather than online.

Please note, some of the information requested on this website is voluntary and some is mandatory. If you choose not to disclose mandatory information during particular transactions, you will not be able to complete the transaction online. You will need to use a non-web option for completing the request.

The Personally Identifiable Information we collect when you use our site(s) may include:

  * your name
  * mailing address 
  * phone number
  * e-mail address
  * identification numbers (i.e. case number) 
  * login names and passwords

**Opt-in / Opt-out**  
We offer you every opportunity to opt out of the email newsletter communication by simply clicking “unsubscribe” within the content of the newsletter. If you request to “opt-out” of future communication, we will honor your request immediately. On every piece of email communication we also provide our physical address and phone contact information.

**Public Records**  
Under Florida law, e-mail addresses are public records. If you do not want your e-mail address released in response to a public-records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity. Instead, contact this office by phone or in writing. Note that information provided through online means becomes public records and is subject to the same access requirements as if submitted on paper.

**Security**  
The Orange County Clerk of Courts is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have physical, electronic/network and managerial procedures in place to safeguard and secure the information we collect and provide. We use internet encryption software when collecting or transferring sensitive data.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns about the Orange County Clerk of Courts’ Privacy Statement, please send an email to Webmaster with “Privacy Statement” in the subject line.
